Guide to the Stanford University, Public Affairs Office, Records of the Vice President
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Original accession, 1960-1980
  - Football
    - San Jose State, Sept. 25, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - University of Washington, Oct. 16, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Oregon State, Oct. 30, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - USC, Nov. 6, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Football, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Football: Special Guests, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - San Jose State, Sept. 27, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Army, Oct. 4, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - UCLA, Oct. 11, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Washington State, Oct. 25, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Oregon, Nov. 15, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Football Season, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Illinois Football Game, Sept. 21, 19 74 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - San Jose Football Game, Sept. 28, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Mi chigan Football Game, Oct. 5, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Washington Football Game, Oct.. 19, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Oregon State Football Game, Nov. 2, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - USC Foo t ball Game, Nov. 9, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Bi g Game, Nov. 23, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Football Season, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Football Luncheons, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - San Jose St ate Football Game, Sept. 29, 19 73 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - UCLA Football Game, Oct. 13, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Washington State Football Game, Oct. 27, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Pennsylvania State Football Game (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Oregon Foo tb al l Game, Nov. 17, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - California Football Game, Nov. 24, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Football Games/Luncheons, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Football - Big Game, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Football: General, 1971-72 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Football Fall, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - University of Oregon, Sept. 25, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Duke, Oct. 2, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - USC, Oct. 16, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Hashi ngt o State, Oct. 23, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - UCLA, Nov. 6, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - San Jose State, Nov. 13, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - California - Big Game, Nov. 20, 19 71 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Ford Founda tion, 1966-71 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Ford Foundation, 1962-65 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Ford Foundation: Academic Administrative Internship Program, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Ford Foundation: Academic Administrative Internship Program, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Ford Foundation Business, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Ford, Congressman Gerald (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Foreign Campuses, 1968-69 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Foreign Policy, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Foreign Students, 1963-73 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Foreign Visitors, Office of, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Foreign Visitors, Office of, 1968- 69 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Foreign Visitors and Students Committee, 1963- 64 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Fraternity: Delta Tau Delta Fraternity, 1976-77 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Free University of Berlin, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Frenchman's Terrace, 1973-76 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Government Policy, 1971-73 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Government Relations (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Education Proposal/AAU, 1973-74 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Graduate Education: Study (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Program, T.A.s (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Grammarian (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, 1969-72 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - International Association of Universities (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - International Relations Program (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - International Studies (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Investment Responsibility Committee, Dec. 1977-Aug. 1978 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Investment Responsibility, June 1, 1977-Dec. 31, 19 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Investment Responsibility, May 15, 1977-May 31, 197 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Investment Responsibility, May 1, 1977-May 15, 19 77 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Investment Responsibility, through April 27, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Iranian Crisis /Immigra tion, 1974- 80 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - International Research and Exchange Board (IREX), 1969-75 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Japan/Fundraising, 1973-74 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Leo Labedz/Conference, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Listening Post (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Medical School, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Middle East Studies/Center, 1978-81 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Review of Minority Student Program, Funding by Ford Founda tion, 1967-73 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Minorities: Black Student Union (BSU), 1968-71 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Minorities: Black Student Union Demands, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Minorities: Black Studies at Stanford - St. Clair Drake (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Minorities: Employment (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Minorities: Emploment, Personnel, 1968-70 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Minorities: Enrollment, Statistics, Reports (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Minorities: Faculty /Staff (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Minori ties: Financial Aid for Students and Programs, 1968-70 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Minorities: Graduate Division, 1968-71 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Minorities: Pilot Program, Task Force on Minority Admiss ions, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Minorities: Special Program Task Force, 1968- 70 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Mount Kisko Ford Foundation, Sept. 14-15, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - NAICU - National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities (Association began in 1975-77) (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - NCAA, Sept. 1976-May 1977 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - NCAA: Financial Needs, Jan. 1976-Aug. 1976 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - National Council on Philanthropy, Dec. 3-5, 1975, Meeting. (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities - Afro and Chicano Studies, 1969-76 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - National Endowment for t he Humanities, 1972- 74 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - National Institute for Transla t ion and Interpret ati, Overseas Campuses, 1973-76 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Pacific-10 Conference, May 20-21, 1978, Corvallis, Oregon (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Pacific-10 Conference (Pac-8 Expanded) (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Personnel and Employee Relations, 1968-74 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Personnel Goals, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Private Colleges and Universities (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Public Affairs Office, 1974-78 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Public Affairs Office: Budget, 1974-76 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Public Affairs: Intern Program, 1974-77 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Public Events, 1973-75 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Public Events, 1975-77 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Public Events/Lively Arts, 1975-80 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Public Events: Search Committee for Director, 1977 Holt Appointment (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1973-75 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - ROTC, 1970-74 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Solicitation, 1976-77 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Spencer Fund Proposals (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Elementary School, 1969-70 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Today and Tomorrow Committees, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Swine Flu: Ramifications (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Travel (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Tressider Memorial Union (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Trustees, Jan. 1973- Ju1y, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Trustees, 1976- 80 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Trustee Elections, 1973-80 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Trustees: Student Membership, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Undergraduate Studies (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Unexcused Absences (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - United Fund/CHAD (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - United Nations (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - United Stanford Employees (USE), 1974-79 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Univers ity Relations, 1971-74 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - University Relations, 1964-71 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - University Relations: Guide Service, 1974-75 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Urban Coalition - Palo Alto (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Visitors, beginning 1980 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Visitors, 1975- 79 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Wage and Price Control Program (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Warsaw (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Watergate (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - White House Advisory Groups on Science and Technology (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Women, 1969-79 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Woodrow Wilson Hogh School (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - World Affairs Council of Northern California (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - World Af fairs Council: Asilimar Conference, May 2-4, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - World Affairs Council: Asilimar Congerence Committe, May 2-4, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Sit-Ins/Student Unrest, 1970-77 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Sit-Ins: Hospital, Spring 1971 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Sit-Ins: A3H (April 3rd Movement) Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Sit-Ins: A3H Information (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Sit-Ins: Correspondence, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Sit-Ins: Facul ty Senate Ac tions, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Sit-Ins: Faculty and AEL Community Statements, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Sit-Ins: Information, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Sit-Ins: Injunction Proceedings, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Sit-Ins: AEL- SRI Correspondence #1 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Sit-Ins: AEL-SRI Correspondence #2 (beginning Nat, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Sit-Ins: AEL- SRI Info rmation #1 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Sit-Ins: AEL- SRI Information #2 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Sit-Ins: AEL- SRI Additional (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Sit-Ins: Against CIA, Oct-Nov 1967 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Sit-Ins: Encina Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Sit- Ins: Encina Information (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Sit-Ins: Old Union, LEN Letters, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Sit-Ins: Old Union, May 1968 #1 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Sit-Ins: Old Union, May 1968 #2 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Sit-Ins: Old Union, May 1968 #3 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Additional Material, 1960-1980; Accession ARCH-1986-033
  Correspondence, minutes, memoranda, reports, speeches, and other records, 1960-1980, generated by Robert M. Rosenzweig, Vice President for Public Affairs, and his predecessor Lyle M. Nelson, Director of University Relations. Among the issues covered by these records are faculty history, honor code, minorities, relations with federal groups such as NDEA, NEH, NSF, Stanford News Service, overseas campuses, parent's day, campus police, politics and political figures, research, and ROTC. Correspondence and speeches of Presidents Kenneth S. Pitzer and Richard W. Lyman are also included.
  - ENVIRONMENT: 1969-74 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - EM (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - FACULTY: History, 1964- 72 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - FACULTY: History, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - FACULTY: Disclosure outside professional activities (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - FACULTY: Political Action Groups 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - FETAL RESEARCH: 1972-73 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - FILM: Proposals & Production 1964- 69 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - FILMS ABOUT STANFORD: 1960-71 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - FOOTBALL/ATHLETICS: John Elway (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - FOOTBALL (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - FOOTBALL (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - FOREIGN INTERESTS: Universities & Colleges (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - FOREIGN I NTERESTS: Scholars (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - FOUNDATION: Ford (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - FOXHUNTJNG (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - FUNDMISING (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - FRATERNITIES - Z Psi (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - SORORITIES (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - FRAUDUI.ENCE (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - FREEDOM OF INFORMATION ACT (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - FROST AMPHITHEATRE (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - GLAS (Gay and Lesbian Alliance at Stanford) (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - GENERAL INFORMATION (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - GENERAL MEHOS (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - GI BILL (Federal) (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - GOVERNANCE OF UNIVERSITY (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - HANDICAPPED (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - HEALTH CARE PROGRAM (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - HEALTH - Friends of (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - HEALTH INSURANCE - National (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - HIGHER EDUCATION INTERNSHIP (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - HONOR CODE (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - HONOR CODE 112 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - HOOVER INSTITUTION (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - HOOVER MEDAL (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - HORTON (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - HOSPITAL: University (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - HOSPITAL: HMP Contract (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - HOTELS (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - HUMAN RELATIONS (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - HUMAN RELATIONS RESEARCH (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - IMMIGRATION (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - INTERNAL AUDIT (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - IRS: International Traffic in Arms (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - INSTITUTE OF PUBLIC POLICY ANALYSIS (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - JASPER RIDGE (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - KENNEDY, D.: Elected 1980 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - LAETRILE (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - LAFCO: Local Agency Formation Commission 1967-69 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - LYHAN, Jing (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - LYMAN, R.: Calendar 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - LYMAN, R.: Calendar 1974-75 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - LYMAN, R.: China Trip (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - LYMAN, R.: Correspondence 1969-70 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - LYMAN, R.: Correspondence 1970-71 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - LYMAN, R.: Correspondence 1971-72 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - LYMAN, R.: Correspondence 1972-73 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - LYMAN, R.: Correspondence 1973-74 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - LYMAN, R.: Functions (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - LYMAN, R.: KZSU (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - LYMAN, R.: Scheduling (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - LYMAN, R.: Speeches 1969-70 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - LYMAN, R.: Speeches 1971- 72 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - LYMAN, R.: Speeches 1972-3 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - LYMAN, R.: Speeches 1973- 4 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - LYMAN, R.: Speeches 1974- 76 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - LYMAN, R.: State of the University 1974-75 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - LYMAN, R.: Washington Trip (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - LYMAN, R.: Statements beg. 1970 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - MEDICAL CENTER: Medical. .. Care (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - MILLER, William (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - MORSE, Senator Wayne (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - MOTHER'S CLUB (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - MUIRHEAD (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - MUSIC (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - NATIONAL ACADEMY OF SCIENCES (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - NATIONAL ACCELERATOR LAB: 1970 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - NASA (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - NATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF COLLEGES AND UNIVERSITIES (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - NATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF COLLEGES AND UNIVERSITIES (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - McCLOSKEY, Paul (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - McCLOSKEY, P: Campaign (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - McCLOSKEY, Paul (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - l'lINORITIES AT STANFORD: 1969-75 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - MINORITIES AT STANFORD: thru Dec. 1968 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - MINORITIES AT STANFORD: American Indian (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - MINORITIES AT STANFORD: Aid (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - MINORITIES AT STANFORD: Asian American (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - MINORITIES AT STANFORD: Enrollment Information 1970-71 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - MINORITIES: General (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - MISCELLANEOUS: Addresses (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - MISCELLANEOUS LETTERS (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - MISCELLANEOUS: Requests to and from other Universities (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - MITCHELL, John: U.S. Attorney General (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - NATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF STATE UNIVERSITIES AND LAND GRANT COLLEGES (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - NATIONAL BUREAU OF ECONOMIC RESEARCH PROGRAMS (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - NATIONAL COLLEGIATE ATHLETIC ASSOCIATION (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - NDEA EXTENSION: HR 4955 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - NDEA INSTITUTE: Title 1/68 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - NEDA INSTITUTE: Title VI/1970 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - NEDA: Title V Cutbacks (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - NATIONAL FOUNDATION ON .. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - NATIONAL ENDOWMENT FOR THE HUMANITIES (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - NATIONAL GOALS (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF EDUCATION (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF EDUCATION (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - NLRB: 1971-72 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - NLRB (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - NATIONAL MEDAL OF SCIENCE: Stanford Recipients (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - NATIONAL RESEARCH UNIVERSITY (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - NSF (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - NSF (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - NSF (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - NSF: Appropriations (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - NSF BOARD: June 14, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - NSF: Cuts (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - NSF: Expenditure, ceiling (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - NATIONAL SERVICE (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - NATIONAL VISITORS TO HANNA HONEYCOMB: 1979 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - NELSON, Robert: Bombing (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - NEPOTISM (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - NEWMAN, Frank: 1970-80 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - SPECIAL TASK FORCE: HEW 1971 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - SPECIAL TASK FORCE: HEW 1971 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - NEWMAN REPORT: beg. 1971 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - NEWSPAPERS & MAGAZINE CLIPPINGS (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - NEWS SERVICE:, 1971-72. (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - NEWS SERVICE:, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - NEWS & PUBLICATIONS ANNUAL REPORT:, 1970-71. (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - NEWS SERVICE: 1969-70 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - NEWS AND PUBLICATIONS: From Frank Newman & Bob Byers (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - News Service, 1967 Jan - Dec 1968 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - News Service (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - News Service: Space Problem (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Nixon: Impeachment, 1973 Oct 23 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Nobel Prize Winners (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Nobel Prize Dinner honoring Burton Richter, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Nuclear power proliferation (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Nurses' strike (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Observer: letters to the editor, 1967 Jan (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Observer: general, 1969 Oct (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Observer, 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Olmsted exhibitions, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Ombudsman (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Operation Share, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Opinion surveys, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Overseas centers, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Overseas centers: Stanford in Austria (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Overseas centers: Stanford in Beruit (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Overseas centers: Stanford in Berlin (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Overseas centers: Stanford in Britain (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Overseas centers: Stanford Center for Chinese Studies (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Overseas centers: Stanford in France (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Overseas centers: Stanford in Germany (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Overseas centers: Stanford in Germany--10th Anniversary, 1968 Jun 29 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Overseas centers: Stanford in Italy (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Overseas centers: Stanford Center for Japanese Studies (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Overseas centers: News Coverage (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Overseas centers: Poland Center, University of Warsaw (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Overseas centers: Rome Classics Center (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Overseas travel tax, 1968 Winter (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Palo Alto: General, 1965-1969 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Palo Alto Stanford Hospital, 1968 Jul (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Pac 10 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Packard, David (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Page Mill Road: Freeway, etc. (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Palmieri, Victor H. (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - PALO ALTO: General beg. Jan. 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - PALO ALTO: Chamber of Commerce (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - PALO ALTO: General Plan (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - PALO ALTO: Materials (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - PARENT'S DAY: 1967 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - PARENT'S DAY: 1967 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - PARENT'S DAY: 1968-9 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - PARENT'S DAY INFORMATION: beg. 1970 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - PARENT'S DAY: 1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - PARENT'S DAY: 1975 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - PARENT 'S DAY: 1976-77 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - PARKING (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - PARKING at Stanford (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - PATENT POLICY (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - PAULING, Dr. Linus (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - PAVILION, Old (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - PEACE CORPS (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - PELL, Claiborne (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - PENNSYLVANIA AGREEMENT (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - PERCY, Senator Charles (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - PERSONNEL: Task Force on Policies and Practices (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - PERSONNEL: Summer Festival Applicants (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - PHI BETA KAPPA (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - PHOTO: Reproduction Services (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - PIKE RESIDENCE (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - PIKE HOUSE and PHOTOS (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - THE PILL (CONTRACEPTIVES): Information, Correspondence, etc (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - PITZER, Dr. K. S.: Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - PITZER, DR. K.S.: Information (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - PITZER INAUGURATION (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - PITZER: Pre-Stanford Speeches (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - PITZER, DR. K.S.: Resignation (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - PITZER, DR. K.S.: Speeches (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - PITZER: Speech Materials (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - PLANNING OFFICE (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - MISCELLANEOUS: Newspaper (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - PACE: General (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - PACE: Press Clippings (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - PACE: fI2 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - PLANNING COMMITTEE: Beginning 10/66 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - PLANT SERVICES (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - POLICE LEGISLATION #1 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - POLICE LEGISLATION # 2 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - POLICE LEGISLATION # 3 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - POLICE: Security and Rela t ed Mat ters (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - POLICE: St anford Campus (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - POLICY MATTERS: Stanford (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - POLITICAL ACTIVITIES AND UNIVERSITIES (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - POLITICAL ISSUES: Campus (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - POLITICS, POLITICAL FIGURES: National (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - POLITICS, POLITICAL FIGURES: National (HUAC-House Un American Activities Committee) (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - POLITICS: National (New Nixon Administration) (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - POLITICS, POLITICAL FIGURES: State (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - POLITICS, POLITICAL FIGURES: State - Stanford Dinner for Stat e Officials, Jan. 22, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - POLITICS, POLITICAL FIGURES: State and Local (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - POLITICS FOR PUBLIC PROGRAM: Sor Studen t s (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - POLITICAL SCIENCE: Department of, beginning 1970 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - POOR PEOPLE AND CAMPAIGN STUDY IN WASHINGTON - Spring 1968 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - POPULATION (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - PORTOLA VALLEY (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - POSTAL MATTERS (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - PRE- REGISTRATION PROGRAM (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - PRESIDENTIAL: Office bombing, Spring 1971 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - PRESIDENT ' S RECEPTION: Palo Al t o Alumni Club 10- 18- 78 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - CHRISTMAS CARD LIST FOR PRESIDENT (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - PRESIDENT ' S OFFICE STAFF: Meetings~ etc (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - PRESIDENT'S REPORTS (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - PRESIDENTIAL DINNER FOR EMERITUS FACULTY: 1975 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - PRESIDENTIAL SCHOLARS (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - PRESIDENTIAL SELECTION: Advisory Committee on (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - PRINCETON PLAN (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - PROPOSAL PREPARATION GUIDE (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - PROVOST'S OFFICEL William F. Miller (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - PROVOST MILLER's CALENDAR: 1972 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - PROVOST's OFFICE: R. W. Lyman (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - PROXMIRE, WILLIAM (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - psi PARTICLE DISCOVERY (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - PSYCHOLOGY (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - PUBLIC AFFAIRS FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - PUBLIC AFFAIRS INTERNSHIPS (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - PUBLICATIONS: General Info, Correspondence, etc. III thru June 1967 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - PUBLICATIONS: General Info, Correspondence, etc. 112 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - PUBLICATIONS: Approaching Stanford (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Student: Daily #1 thru Dec. 1970 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Student: Daily #2 beg. 1/71 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - PUBLICATIONS, Student: (Daily) Rose Bowl Book (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - PUBLICATIONS, Student: -Li-ve -O-ak (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - PUBLICATIONS, Stanford Review (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - PUBLICATIONS: Stanford Today, July 1969 thru Dec. 1972 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - PUBLICATIONS: Stanford Today thru June 1969 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - PUBLICATIONS: Stanford Today and Tomorrow (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - PUBLICATIONS, Student: General (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - PUBLICATIONS: Western Politica (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - PUBLICATIONS SERVICE (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - PUBLIC AFFAIRS: Staff Retreat, 3/30/79 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - PUBLIC EVENTS- beg. 1973 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - PUBLIC EVENTS- beg. 1976 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - PUBLIC EXERCISES, Committee on, ilL (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - PUBLIC EXERCISES, Committee on, 112 (Box 8, Folder 19)